{"test_questions": [[{"question": "After driving professor Kumar to the museum she dropped him at his hotel.", "opta": "After being driven to the museum, Professor Kumar was dropped at his hotel.", "optb": "Professor Kumar was being driven dropped at his hotel.", "optc": "After she had driven Professor Kumar to the museum she had dropped him at his hotel.", "optd": "After she was driven Professor Kumar to the museum she had dropped him at his hotel.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "I remember my sister taking me to the museum.", "opta": "I remember I was taken to the museum by my sister.", "optb": "I remember being taken to the museum by my sister.", "optc": "I remember myself being taken to the museum by my sister.", "optd": "I remember taken to the museum by my sister.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Who is creating this mess?", "opta": "Who has been created this mess?", "optb": "By whom has this mess been created?", "optc": "By whom this mess is being created?", "optd": "By whom is this mess being created?", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "They greet me cheerfully every morning.", "opta": "Every morning I was greeted cheerfully.", "optb": "I am greeted cheerfully by them every morning.", "optc": "I am being greeted cheerfully by them every morning.", "optd": "Cheerful greeting is done by them every morning to me.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Darjeeling grows tea.", "opta": "Tea is being grown in Darjeeling.", "optb": "Let the tea be grown in Darjeeling.", "optc": "Tea is grown in Darjeeling.", "optd": "Tea grows in Darjeeling.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "They have built a perfect dam across the river.", "opta": "Across the river a perfect dam was built.", "optb": "A perfect dam has been built by them across the river.", "optc": "A perfect dam should have been built by them.", "optd": "Across the river was a perfect dam.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Do you imitate others?", "opta": "Are others being imitated by you?", "optb": "Are others imitated by you?", "optc": "Have others being imitated by you?", "optd": "Were others being imitated by you?", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "You need to clean your shoes properly.", "opta": "Your shoes are needed to clean properly.", "optb": "You are needed to clean your shoes properly.", "optc": "Your shoes need to be cleaned properly.", "optd": "Your shoes are needed by you to clean properly.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "He is said to be very rich.", "opta": "He said he is very rich.", "optb": "People say he is very rich.", "optc": "He said it is very rich.", "optd": "People say it is very rich.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The invigilator was reading out the instructions.", "opta": "The instructions were read by the invigilator.", "optb": "The instructions were being read out by the invigilator.", "optc": "The instructions had been read out by the invigilator.", "optd": "The instructions had been read by the invigilator.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "You can play with these kittens quite safely.", "opta": "These kittens can played with quite safely.", "optb": "These kittens can play with you quite safely.", "optc": "These kittens can be played with you quite safely.", "optd": "These kittens can be played with quite safely.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A child could not have done this mischief.", "opta": "This mischief could not be done by a child.", "optb": "This mischief could not been done by a child.", "optc": "This mischief could not have been done by a child.", "optd": "This mischief a child could not have been done.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "James Watt discovered the energy of steam.", "opta": "The energy of steam discovered James Watt.", "optb": "The energy of steam was discovered by James Watt.", "optc": "James Watt was discovered by the energy of steam.", "optd": "James Watt had discovered energy by the steam.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "She makes cakes every Sunday.", "opta": "Every Sunday cakes made by her.", "optb": "Cakes are made by her every Sunday.", "optc": "Cakes make her every Sunday.", "optd": "Cakes were made by her every Sunday.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "She spoke to the official on duty.", "opta": "The official on duty was spoken to by her", "optb": "The official was spoken to by her on duty.", "optc": "She was spoken to by the official on duty.", "optd": "She was the official to be spoken to on duty.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The doctor advised the patient not to eat rice.", "opta": "The patient was advised by the doctor not to eat rice.", "optb": "The patient was advised by the doctor that he should not eat rice.", "optc": "The patient was being advised by the doctor that he should not rice by the doctor.", "optd": "The patient has been advised not to eat rice by the doctor.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "I cannot accept your offer.", "opta": "Your offer cannot be accepted by me.", "optb": "I cannot be accepted by your offer.", "optc": "The offer cannot be accepted by me.", "optd": "Your offer cannot be accepted.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "You should open the wine about three hours before you use it.", "opta": "Wine should be opened about three hours before use.", "optb": "Wine should be opened by you three hours before use.", "optc": "Wine should be opened about three hours before you use it.", "optd": "Wine should be opened about three hours before it is used.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "They will inform the police.", "opta": "The police will be informed by them.", "optb": "The police will inform them.", "optc": "The police are informed by them.", "optd": "Informed will be the police by them.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}